<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Poppy Nightingale</title>
    <link href="https://poppynightingale.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://poppynightingale.github.io" />
    <updated>2025-05-30T10:31:02+01:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Poppy Nightingale</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://poppynightingale.github.io</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Welcome </title>
        <author>
            <name>Poppy Nightingale</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://poppynightingale.github.io/welcome.html"/>
        <id>https://poppynightingale.github.io/welcome.html</id>

        <updated>2025-05-30T10:31:02+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Hello everyone, and a massive, warm welcome to my brand new website! I'm Poppy, and I'm absolutely thrilled to embark&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
  <p>
    Hello everyone, and a massive, warm welcome to my brand new website!
<br>I'm Poppy, and I'm absolutely thrilled to embark on this incredible journey as a new author. For as long as I can remember, I've been passionate about reading, writing and creating new worlds for people to get lost in!
<br>Big news! My debut novel, 'Heart Of The Ormran Warrior' a spicy adult Sci-Fi romance packed with adventure is launching on January 1st, 2026! I'm absolutely buzzing with excitement to share it with you!
<br>Over the coming weeks and months, I plan to share:
  </p>

  <ul>
    <li>The Journey to Publication: I'll be sharing behind-the-scenes glimpses of the writing and editing process.</li>
  </ul>

  <ul>
    <li>Sneak Peeks &amp; Teasers: Get early hints about the story, characters, and world of my upcoming book.</li>
  </ul>

  <ul>
    <li>Cover Reveal Countdown: Be among the first to see the cover!</li>
  </ul>

  <ul>
    <li>Launch Updates &amp; Pre-order Info: All the details as we get closer to the big day.</li>
  </ul>

  <ul>
    <li>Bookish Chats &amp; Inspirations: Let's talk about our favourite reads, writing, and everything that sparks creativity!</li>
  </ul>

  <p>
    I truly believe that stories connect us, and I can't wait to connect with all of you. This is the very beginning, and I'd be honoured to have you join me on this adventure.
<br><br>Let the countdown begin! 
<br>Warmly,
<br>Poppy&nbsp;<br>
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
